CURRICULUM VITAE

José Waiman

Nationality: Argentino (30351790N) e Italiano (YB299313)

Phone: +54 2914624231 (WhatsApp)

E-Mail: josewaiman@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

As a professional with more than 10 years of experience in administration and management of tourism enterprises, I have proven skills in administrative and accounting positions, as well as in the leadership of bilingual guides and restaurants.

In the last 2 years ago, I have been studying and applying my knowledge in different programming languages and I have fallen in love with computer science. Now, I am looking to start a career in this exciting sector and develop myself professionally.

I am a proactive, responsible, committed person with a positive attitude. I have teamwork skills, decision making, problem solving and good empathy skills. Also, I am always willing to learn and improve.

ACADEMIC TRAINING

- First year student of Bachelor of Computer Science. (UNS). 2023
- Diploma in full stack web programming with React JS (UTN BA). Start: 06/15/22. End: 12/12/2022.
- Postgraduate Diploma in Tourism Management (Blas Pascal University). 2020.
- Postgraduate Diploma in Business Management (UNS). 2020.
- Degree in tourism. National University of the South (UNS). 2014.
- Bachelor with orientation in Economics and Management of organizations (UNS). 2004.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Sales Manager, Ventania Travel.

Responsible for the administration and reservation of cabin rentals, sale of long-distance bus tickets and reception and dispatch of Correo Argentino parcels. November 2020 to present. Villa Ventana, Buenos Aires, Argentina.

- Resident Manager, Estancia San Lorenzo. Hired by: Argentina Vision S.A. 2018-2020.
- Administrative-Accounting Manager in tourist establishment. Employed by: S.A Estancias Harberton. 2014-2018.
- Tourist Guide, specialist in the Valdés Peninsula Area. Bilingual guide in English and Italian. Employed by: Argentina Visión S.A. 2009-2014.

LANGUAGES

- ENGLISH: Lower Intermediate. Conversational.
- ITALIAN: Lower Intermediate. Conversational.
- PORTUGUESE: Lower Intermediate. Conversational.

PROGRAMMING COURSES

- Machine Learning (G-Talent.net). February 2021.
- Web Development from Scratch, HTML, CSS and Javascript (Udemy). February 2021.
- Python, R Studio and SQL (a2capacitacion.com).

CURSOS DE IDIOMAS

- ABA English B2 (115 horas). 29/04/2019. Barcelona
- ABA English B1 (101 horas). 07/08/2018. Barcelona
- ABA English A2 (87 horas). 20/07/2018. Barcelona
- ABA English A1 (72 horas). 20/07/2018. Barcelona
- Face-to-face English Course for 11 weeks held at IH Cape Town (South Africa).
- Grammar of Portuguese Lingua. Dictared by: Ricardo Sabbag.

COURSES AND ACADEMIC TALKS

- Postgraduate Course: Strategic Planning. UNS
- Postgraduate Course: Business Finance. UNS
- · Postgraduate Course: Quality Management. UNS
- · Postgraduate Course: Cash Management. UNS.
- · Postgraduate Course: Strategic Distribution Marketing. UNS
- Level 1 Intelligence Analyst certification.
- · Seminar Workshop: "Quality and differentiation in the new types of accommodation."
- Course: "Planning and management of the quality of destinations and companies". November 2011.
- · Course: "Rural sociology applied to tourism and social and cultural representations of tourism and rural areas."